"use strict";(self.webpackChunkreact_quiz=self.webpackChunkreact_quiz||[]).push([[755],{755:function(e,t,n){n.r(t);t.default=[{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u6551\u751f\u54e1\u5982\u5728\u6c99\u7058\u70ba\u6eba\u8005\u5b89\u653e\u5fa9\u7526\u59ff\u52e2\uff0c\u6eba\u8005\u7684\u8eab\u9ad4\u61c9\u8207\u6d77\u908a\u5782\u76f4\u9762\u90e8\u80cc\u6d77\uff0c\u4ee5\u6709\u5229\u5206\u6ccc\u6216\u5614\u5410\u7269\u5f9e\u53e3\u4e2d\u6d41\u51fa\u3002",answers:[{type:"F",content:"O"},{type:"T",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u82e5\u53e3\u5167\u6709\u7570\u7269\u6642\uff0c\u4e0d\u5fc5\u4f7f\u7528\u624b\u6307\u6e05\u9664\u53e3\u5167\u7570\u7269\u5f8c\uff0c\u518d\u58d3\u984d\u62ac\u8d77\u4e0b\u5df4\uff0c\u4ee5\u66a2\u901a\u50b7\u60a3\u7684\u547c\u5438\u9053\u3002",answers:[{type:"F",content:"O"},{type:"T",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u5152\u7ae5\u547c\u5438\u9053\u54fd\u585e\u6025\u6551\u8853\uff1a\u62cd\u80cc5\u4e0b\u3001\u58d3\u80f85\u4e0b\u3001\u6e05\u9664\u53e3\u8154\u7570\u7269\u3001\u62ac\u9ad8\u4e0b\u5df4\u3001\u53e3\u5c0d\u53e3\u4eba\u5de5\u547c\u5438\u3002",answers:[{type:"F",content:"O"},{type:"T",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u54c8\u59c6\u7acb\u514b\u6cd5\u64cd\u4f5c\u662f\u4f7f\u6a6b\u8188\u819c\u7a81\u7136\u5411\u4e0a\uff0c\u58d3\u8feb\u80ba\u90e8\uff0c\u4ee5\u4f7f\u963b\u585e\u6c23\u7ba1\u4e4b\u7570\u7269\u5674\u51fa\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u91cd\u5ea6\u547c\u5438\u9053\u54fd\u585e\u75c7\u72c0\u662f\uff1a\u7121\u6cd5\u8aaa\u8a71\u3001\u7121\u6cd5\u547c\u5438\u3001\u7121\u6cd5\u54b3\u55fd\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u8f15\u5ea6\uff08\u90e8\u4efd\uff09\u547c\u5438\u9053\u54fd\u585e\u75c7\u72c0\u662f\uff1a\u8aaa\u8a71\u56f0\u96e3\u3001\u547c\u5438\u56f0\u96e3\u3001\u54b3\u55fd\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u547c\u5438\u9053\u7570\u7269\u54fd\u585e\u7684\u6392\u9664\u6cd5\u6709\uff1a\u6307\u6df1\u4f38\u6cd5\u3001\u8179\u63a8\u6cd5\u3001\u80f8\u58d3\u6cd5\u3001\u80cc\u64ca\u6cd5\u3001\u81ea\u6551\u6cd5\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"TrueORFalse",question:"\u5fa9\u7526\u59ff\u52e2\u7684\u7528\u9014\u662f\u8655\u7406\u4e0d\u7701\u4eba\u4e8b\uff0c\u800c\u6709\u547c\u5438\u53ca\u8840\u6db2\u5faa\u74b0\u5fb5\u8c61\u7684\u60a3\u8005\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"O"},{type:"F",content:"X"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u8655\u7406\u6e05\u9192\u7684\u54fd\u585e\u60a3\u8005\uff0c\u61c9\u63a1\u7528\u4ee5\u4e0b\u59ff\u52e2\u5411\u4e0a\u63a8\u58d3\u80f8\u8154\u5e95\u90e8\uff084\uff09\u8b93\u60a3\u8005\u8eba\u4e0b\uff0c\u5411\u4e0b\u63a8\u58d3\u8179\u90e8\u3002",answers:[{type:"T",content:"\u8b93\u60a3\u8005\u7ad9\u7acb\uff0c\u4ee5\u524d\u5f13\u5f8c\u7bad\u7684\u65b9\u5f0f\u63e1\u63a8\u80f8\u8154\u5e95\u90e8"},{type:"F",content:"\u8b93\u60a3\u8005\u7ad9\u7acb\uff0c\u4e0d\u4e88\u7406\u6703\u8b93\u60a3\u8005\u8eba\u4e0b"},{type:"F",content:"\u8b93\u60a3\u8005\u8eba\u4e0b\uff0c"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u5fa9\u7526\u59ff\u52e2\u5be6\u65bd\u5f8c\u9700",answers:[{type:"F",content:"10\u5206"},{type:"F",content:"20\u5206"},{type:"T",content:"30\u5206"},{type:"F",content:"1\u5c0f\u6642 \u7ffb\u8eab\u4e00\u6b21\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u5c0d\u5b55\u5a66\u5be6\u65bd\u7684\u54c8\u59c6\u7acb\u514b\u6025\u6551\u6cd5\uff0c\u61c9\u63a1\u7528",answers:[{type:"F",content:"\u8179\u90e8\u63a8\u64ca\u6cd5"},{type:"T",content:"\u80f8\u90e8\u63a8\u64e0\u6cd5"},{type:"F",content:"\u80cc\u90e8\u6572\u64ca\u6cd5"},{type:"F",content:"\u5012\u7acb\u6cd5\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u547c\u5438\u9053\u54fd\u585e\u7684\u7665\u8c61\u662f",answers:[{type:"F",content:"\u4e0d\u80fd\u8aaa\u8a71"},{type:"F",content:"\u547c\u5438\u56f0\u96e3"},{type:"F",content:"\u96d9\u624b\u7dca\u6293\u5589\u56a8"},{type:"T",content:"\u4ee5\u4e0a\u7686\u662f\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u6025\u6551\u4e2d\u60a3\u8005\u5614\u5410\u6642\uff0c\u8a72\u5982\u4f55\u8655\u7f6e\uff1f",answers:[{type:"F",content:"\u62cd\u6253\u60a3\u8005\u80cc\u90e8"},{type:"F",content:"\u6e05\u6d17\u60a3\u8005\u53e3\u8154"},{type:"T",content:"\u60a3\u8005\u5074\u81e5\u5c07\u5614\u5410\u7269\u6316\u51fa"},{type:"F",content:"\u5c07\u60a3\u8005\u4e0b\u534a\u8eab\u62ac\u9ad8\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u4e00\u822c\u610f\u8b58\u4e0d\u6e05\u7684\u60a3\u8005\uff0c\u9069\u5408\u63a1\u7528\u7684\u59ff\u52e2\u662f\u54ea\u4e00\u7a2e\uff1f",answers:[{type:"F",content:"\u534a\u81e5\u5750"},{type:"F",content:"\u62ac\u9ad8\u8173\u90e8"},{type:"T",content:"\u5fa9\u7526\u59ff\u52e2"},{type:"F",content:"\u4fef\u81e5\u3002"}]},{questionType:"multipleChoice",question:"\u60a3\u8005\u660f\u8ff7\u3001\u7121\u547c\u5438\uff0c\u6709\u8108\u640f\u6642\uff0c\u6700\u6709\u6548\u7684\u6025\u6551\u6cd5\u662f",answers:[{type:"T",content:"\u4eba\u5de5\u547c\u5438"},{type:"F",content:"CPR"},{type:"F",content:"\u54c8\u59c6\u7acb\u514b\u6cd5\u3002"}]}]}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=755.b42dd717.chunk.js.map